Those who ceaselessly hone the art
of killing are known as masters.
These lethal abilities, dutifully
passed down through many generations,
have become what are
called modified bloodlines.
This is the story of one such master,
Hikaru Gero of the Poison Clan
and his greatest challenge yet,
to get married.
No mama, lots of time?
Fun, fun, fun, you so cool, no, ba ba ba!
Do you have that tomorrow?
Kill or kiss?
Let's go kilogram Would you who are here?
Hum 무릎?
Above you doing okay?
Let's go!
Kill or kiss.
Yeah girl.
I can't.
Kill, I can't.
Can't kill, I can't.
Just tell me one thing.
You have a first-class boating license.
Why?
Rich middle-aged guys
love being on the water.
I'm like a qualification collector.
I'm IT certified, a secretary, a sommelier,
a color designer, a drone operator.
I'm a cosmetician.
You really are the best in the business.
Looks like Kimmy's
doing all right for now.
But we still don't know how
to get the thing off her.
Even if I need to break
out the truth serum,
I'm going to make the
Beastmasters tell me.
Right!
Thanks for the lift out here,
but this is where we say goodbye.
You've fulfilled your end of the deal.
The hitman hunter isn't
a threat to me now.
All that's left is for me to
face the head of the family on my
own and figure out a way to
convince him to grant me my freedom.
In short, I don't need
you three any longer!
Arashiyama, I know you're trying
to keep us out of danger, but...
Are you going to make me
spell it out for you guys?
No question, this is 100 % a trap!
You're Hikaru Gero from
the Five Great Families!
They're out for you!
I can't take it!
It's not fair.
You shouldn't have to
risk your life for me.
I want to risk it.
There's a voice inside telling me,
if I walk out on you now in your time
of need, I'll never make anyone happy.
Just as long as I get to clean
up the Beast Clan, I'll be fine.
Thanks for the boat right here,
but I need you to wait at the
harbor until I give you a call.
I can't in good conscience ask you
to come along to where we're going.
I'll be prepping for our next matchmaking
strategy, so you'd better come back.
Sure.
I'm thinking that the Beast
Clan's using Arashiyama
as bait to take out Pichi
and me at the same time.
You're the one who's
been hunting them down,
but I don't know what
I did to piss them off.
But it's possible that they
think of me as a business rival.
First a squid, now an eagle?
Is this an ambush?
Arashiyama comes first!
Toxin, step up!
Holy...
Ultra simple how to chop
up squid even if you're
out of your desk um yeah
real sorry i'm gonna
have to cook you up now
there's a surprise who
would have guessed poison
masters can walk on water?
Step one, remove the entrails
from the body of the squid.
Start by placing your squid on a cutting
board, then remove the tentacles.
Now that those pesky things
are out of the way, all right,
take out the guts and then...
Step two, removing the squid's ink.
Slip the body open vertically.
After locating the ink sack,
grab it and pull it out!
Lastly, cut that mollusk
into bite-sized pieces!
Is this...
what Gero was talking about?
It's almost scary how good
this guy is with a knife!
What if...
the café serves squid pasta?
Looks like I'm first up to bat!
No surprise seeing I'm
the world's fastest man!
The living legend, Kota Hamidua!
There's no way this guy is a beastmaster.
I'm guessing he's a birdmaster
from a branch family.
A subcontractor.
Let's hear it.
What's your goal?
Why'd you lure us out here?
You want us dead for some reason.
Hmm.
The hell if I know. Figures.
Even if he did, he wouldn't tell me.
Although,
taking you down will make me so stinking
rich I'll be set for the rest of my days.
Now, I'm under a fancy-pants NDA,
but strictly between you and
me, I'll make tens of billions.
So why involve her?
Because I was told if I nabbed the broad
from you first, the job would be easier.
I'm not thrilled with kidnapping, but I
can't go and let my feelings get in the way.
You won't believe this, but deep down,
I've actually got a heart of gold.
I've only gone against my core
beliefs one time in my entire life.
It was a snowy night, which
was unusual for March.
We were in the middle of practice when the
crane I had formed a
last-minute battery with.
Oh, great.
He's monologuing.
Luckily, this badass swooped
in and took their place.
How do I remove the Bonda Constrictor?
Well, I'd love to tell you.
Just trying to find
out is a serious crime.
Play ball!
You ready, boys?
Time for birch ball!
Take the field!
BANDER UP!
Crap!
Why is he so fast?
His branch must be close
to the main family!
Don't be a chicken or
you're about to be kicking!
If I can face him head-to-head on my
own terms, this game's in the bag.
Making enemies with the poison gland
is stupid, but the money's too good.
He might be from one of
the five great families,
but it's not like they're the top five
families when it comes
to a straight-up fight.
All I need is to hit this out of
the park and my life turns around.
When I finish this job, I'm flying
straight to America, home of baseball,
and breaking free of the rule books.
Wait till they get a load of bird's ball!
How absolutely delicious.
Gato blood.
It's a poor matchup for him.
The Poison Master might
fall to the Bird Master.
You've got it all wrong, Byakko.
It's that bird brain
who's in over his beak.
Man, my heart's racing in anticipation.
I mean, it's obvious, isn't it?
The only reason the
Poison Clan has managed to
survive this long is thanks
to traps and foul play.
Of course he has something planned!
His venomous fangs gnaw away at you, and
by the time you realize what's happening,
it's too late.
I'm so worked up!
I can barely contain myself!
So, Poison Master Hikaru-Gedo,
let's see those tricks of yours.
Entertain me.
Hey, hey!
Well, I'm the winner,
so chicken's for dinner!
Bird!
Bird's ball winning shot!
Foul stadium farewell!
Caw!
There's no place for you
to hide out in the open!
Smoke screen?
Nah, the scent tells me it's
one of his other tricks.
Poison gas!
He's trying to buy himself
time to set up a trap!
Too bad for him we're on the beach.
The sea breeze ought
to clear this up soon.
Still.
Just to be absolutely
sure birdfall reverse
swing avian iron oh he
sucked me where's the trap?
That moron doesn't matter if you are
the fastest guy around birdmaster!
You won't get very far
against skies who don't
play fair the whole point
of a trap is to catch
You off guard that's
what makes them such an
effective technique showing
you his hand was the
Real trap psyching him
out with scented smoke
and straining his resources
was easy i just had to
Wait for the right opening
with some help from
toxin step up i launched
myself and grounded him!
Listen i've still got questions for you
you want to know where the beast master is?
Head up the mountain.
You do realize you're not gonna make
it all the way to the top, right?
How many enemies are there?
Another trick! Nice try!
Some things are secret,
like how the clan mobilized all
the major and minor branches.
Well, in terms of threats, though...
He can't help himself.
It's like he wants to
spill all their secrets.
Want to get the Bonda Constrictor off?
It's never gonna happen.
But I did hear a rumor about
this one time the Beast Clan.
One, two, testing,
testing. Is this thing on?
Hello, Hikaru-geiro.
This is Beastmaster Toshiro Dogo.
Welcome to the Dogo Animal Kingdom.
I am the king of this here rock.
Since we're getting to know each other,
how about clearing up these
stories I keep hearing about?
Word is the future head of the Gato family
keeps taking jobs that don't pay squats.
Changing your line of work, huh?
You're a bodyguard.
I am a bachelor.
I'm looking for a partner.
And as for the jobs, I'm helping
people so I can meet women.
Sure, I used that girl as bait, but
I couldn't figure out why it worked.
I mean, the future heir of the Poison
Clan reeled in by some useless chick.
Mystery solved.
You're considering marrying her.
A word to the wise.
Don't do it.
The Poison Clan has spent
centuries refining their bloodline.
It's an S-tier work of art.
You'd be tanking the whole industry.
A guy like you with
money and power shouldn't
be hurting to score
chicks with good blood.
Lucky for her, she's asleep.
So she doesn't have to
listen to your crap.
Well, this one's smaller.
A spear?
Speaking of marriage, don't Bird and
Spearmaster make the perfect duo?
Bro, never forget that he who
holds the blood holds the power.
It's the dawn of a new era, so I certainly
hope you're on the edge of your seat.
Spearmaster Nagihiko
Kushima, deceased at age 72.
Kill count, 887.
His specialty lies in
the blood of his clan,
which dedicated everything to the spear.
He could unleash 88 silent
thrusts in only one second flat.
This power is blowing my mind!
It's good!
This rules!
I made the right move pledging
loyalty to the Beast Clan.
I'm taking Birds Ball to the
next level as Bird Spearmaster!
He's using another master's abilities.
That doesn't make sense.
Unless it has something to do
with the lead Peachy's following.
Rumor is they're planning something major.
Something dangerous that'll
kill a whole lot of people.
You're on the ropes!
My bird spear's got all the
speed I could ever need.
No stealing bases for you.
I've got the field covered
with my avian alloy bat!
It's called cross-sanguination, my friend.
And I've mixed blood from different clans
to create an entirely new breed of master.
We live in an age of
all-you-can-eat possibilities.
Where's the fun in mastering one
ability when you can master them all?
Well then, what's your move, Gato?
Another sneak attack
won't get you out of this.
Come here, Byakko!
You're going to miss out on the show!
Oh yeah, off to collect
another sample for me.
Talk about rotten timing, though.
PG really hurt himself
trying to protect me.
Never thought the sea
rescue training I picked
up to impress rich surfers would save us.
Somehow we made it past the octopus
bombs that magically appeared,
but the currents tossed us on the
opposite side of the island from Gato.
How did I go from an elegant marriage
swindler to a hopeless castaway?
Huh?
Hello, giant bear.
Magnificent!
Your form is gorgeous!
And I just noticed you're
a black belt! Impressive!
Thank you for showing us your epic moves!
Well, we'd better get going!
Give me your blood!
Of course it wouldn't be that easy!
That's it! Ca-caw!
No more extra innings for you, ghetto!
I'll knock it out of the park!
Here comes the swat song!
A walk-off grand slam!
Birds of a feather are supposed to stick
together my teammates
whiffed on me what did he do
Don't underestimate a
poison master funny you
didn't even notice when
I pulled another one of
My so-called cheap tricks no don't tell me
he let us peck him on
purpose his blood is mixed
with Something I injected
a muscle relaxant I'm
resistant to it with
your friends not so much
Damn it!
I'm not losing to unsportsmanlike conduct!
You're up, my all-stars!
Spurts strike him out!
I'm out!
Oh, Hikaru-Gedo, I've got to
have a taste of your blood.
Soon, I will.
Arashiyama.
Say something. You good?
Oh, yeah. Perfect.
Why would you help me?
Your bleeding will stop
if you remain still.
And, to answer your question,
you're just a baseball enthusiast
who is brainwashed by the bees.
Bird's ball is the avian sport that
transcends the perfection of baseball.
Isn't that right my teammates?
It's a shutout ghetto!
Next time I'm gonna whoop
you fair and square.
I challenge you to a real game.
It won't be a rematch
It's such a shame crossing
the nation smashes
together different bloodlines
but once activated,
they each fight for
dominance within the host.
The end result is death.
You bastard.
Branch families are nothing but
playthings for the main clan.
Dodo was actually a guinea pig, and
Hamster Girl is only holding you back.
You said you wanted that
Bonda constrictor off.
Here's a hint.
The master key is my blood.
So you'd better head over to my place.
The whole clan's here waiting
to get this party started!
Birdbrain pecked out just enough blood.
Well, for now, but I won't be satisfied
until I've drained every last drop.
Poison master.
All I ever wanted was for Bird's
Ball to make the big leagues.
Thanks.
I'm feeling better now.
Piichi, watch out!
Master Toshiro, this is Byakko.
I collected this sample
without difficulty.
I knew this would work, but it's
going smoother than I expected.
I've never been in a better mood.
Here you go, Byakko.
I made this one just for you.
Not while I'm on duty. Huh?
You think you're too
good to play with my toy?
Fine, whatever, I don't really care.
Operation Bloodline Collection is
complete, or blowpleat for short.
The issue with cross-sanguination is your
body rejects the new blood
so hard it wrecks you.
But the Gator family's blood
has adapted to so many toxins?
It neutralizes any adverse reaction.
meaning the host won't
drop dead like that dodo.
As for this Piichi guy,
whoever he is, his blood jacks up
physical and cognitive abilities,
And now they're all mine,
just from lopping off
some branch families.
Now to put these to use.
Byakko, it's time to execute the plan.
And reach our goal, crushing
them once and for all.
My situation keeps getting worse.
Who knows when the Beastmaster will
change his mind and dispose of Arashiyama.
Let's go. Hold it.
You're still not fully recovered.
Sit back down.
But if we waste any more time...
Hey!
It's a handbush!
Shut up and enjoy the warmth of
my thigh pillows while you heal.
Thanks, but I...
I insist.
Let me do something.
For you.
Some master I am.
No one's ever hired me for a job.
The whole clan thinks I'm a joke.
I've never once wanted or
bothered to become stronger.
So now, all I can do is hide
and watch while others get hurt.
If only I had tried harder.
Could things have turned out differently?
Why am I so useless?
If I was more ambitious,
we wouldn't even be here.
You are a master, like me.
When I was so busy focused on helping you,
I never stopped to consider
what you were capable of.
Please, allow me to start
over, Hamster Master!
Let's go, and kick the
Beast Clan's ass together!
I'll be creepy, oh, fake that voice.
Watermaster, lend me a hand.
It's the best fit for you. I love me!
Next time, good for nothing.